Farbstein, Leonard; Papers apap245
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- The 90th Congress, 1962-1968; Undated; 6; 12.4 cubic ft.
  - Foreign Aid Bill (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Foreign Aid Bill (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Foreign Aid Bill: Ch'san Sofer Chason Yecheskel Institute, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Foreign Affairs: Anti-Semitism, 1967; 1970 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Foreign Affairs: Anti-Semitism, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Foreign Affairs: Arab Refugees, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Foreign Affairs: Arab Refugee Proposal, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Affairs: Biafra, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Affairs Committee (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Affairs Committee (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Affairs: Communism, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Affairs: Egypt, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Affairs: Greece, 1968; 1970 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Affairs: India, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Affairs: Iran, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Foreign Affairs: Israel, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Foreign Affairs: Israel- Leonard Farbstein's Trip July 1967 (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Affairs: Israel- Leonard Farbstein's Trip July 1967 (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Affairs: Kiryath Mattersdorf in Israel, LTD., 1965-1968 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Foreign Affairs: Middle East (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Foreign Affairs: Middle East (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Foreign Affairs: Middle East Crisis (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Foreign Affairs: Middle East Crisis (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Foreign Affairs: Middle East Crisis- Israeli Letters, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Foreign Affairs: Near East Report, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Foreign Affairs: Thailand, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - "G" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - General Services Administration, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Government Operations, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - "H" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - H. Con. Res. 53: A Concurrent Resolution for United States Military Personnel Held Captive in Vietnam, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - H. Con. Res. 69: A Concurrent Resolution to Provide for a Permanent United Nations Peacekeeping Force, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - H. Con. Res. 582: A Concurrent Resolution to Recommend Sending the Vietnam Question to the United Nations, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - H. Con. Res. 586: A Concurrent Resolution to Seek United Nations Security Council Consideration of Vietnam Conflict, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - H. Con. Res. 627: A Concurrent Resolution to Require France to Pay Its World War I Debt, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - H. Con. Res. 678: A Concurrent Resolution for the Level of United States Forces Should Not Be Increased in Vietnam Without the Explicit Consent of the Congress, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - H. Con. 711: A Concurrent Resolution to Require Appropriate Committees in Respect to United States Policies in Southeast Asia, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - H. Con. Res. 738: A Concurrent Resolution to Express the Sense of Congress that United States Diplomatic Relations with the United Arab Republic Should Not Be Restored, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - H. Con. Res. 741: A Concurrent Resolution to Recognize the Twenty-Fifth Anniversary of the Warsaw Ghetto Uprising, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - H. Con. Res. 830: A Concurrent Resolution to Liquidate the United States Involvement in Vietnam, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - H. Con. Res. 834: A Concurrent Resolution for Providing Humanitarian Assistance to the Suffering Innocents in the Nigeria-Biafra Area, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - H. J. Res. 126: A Joint Resolution to Designate the Fourth Sunday in September of Each Year as Interfaith Day, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - H. J. Res. 538: A Joint Resolution for the Designation of the Second Week in May of Each Year as "National School Safety Patrol Week", 1967 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - H. J. Res. 656: A Joint Resolution to Consent To and Enter Into the Mid-Atlantic States Air Pollution Control Compact, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - H. J. Res. 1079: A Joint Resolution for Financial Support to Nonprofit Public Educational Broadcasters, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - H. J. Res. 1142: A Joint Resolution for Authorization of a Study of the Feasibility of Establishing a JudiCorps, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - H. J. Res. 1280: A Joint Resolution for a White House Conference on Aging be Called by the President of the United States in 1971, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - H. R. 1991: A Bill for Amendment of Title 2 of the Merchant Marine Act (Also Contains Related Bills), 1967 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - H. R. 2072: A Bill to Provide for Computation of Disability Retirement Pay for Members of the Uniformed Services, 1966-1967; 1969 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - H. R. 2073: A Bill to Amend Title 10 of the United States Code (Also Contains Related Bills), 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - H. R. 2074: A Bill to Establish a United States Committee on Human Rights, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - H. R. 2075: A Bill for Amendment of the Act of August 21, 1935, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - H. R. 2076: A Bill for Amendment of the Bankruptcy Act (Also Contains Related Bills), 1962-1963; 1965; 1967 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - H. R. 2078: A Bill for Amendment of the Bankruptcy Act (Also Contains Related Bills), 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - H. R. 2080: A Bill to Permit a State to Elect to Use Funds from the Highway Trust Fund for Purposes of Urban Mass Transportation (Also Contains Related Bills), 1965; 1967 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - H. R. 2081: A Bill for Amendment of the Social Security Amendments of 1965 (Also Contains H. R. 11885), 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - H. R. 2158: A Bill to Regulate and Foster Commerce by Providing a System for the Taxation of Interstate Commerce, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - H. R. 2608: A Bill for Amendment of the Older Americans Act of 1965 (Also Contains Related Bills), 1967 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - H. R. 2667: A Bill for Authorization of the Transfer of a Vessel to the Lower Manhattan Antipoverty Board (Also Contains Related Bills), 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - H. R. 3047: A Bill for Amendment of the Federal Food, Drug and Cosmetic Act (Also Contains Related Bills), 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - H. R. 3048: A Bill for Amendment of the Public Works and Economic Development Act of 1965, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - H. R. 3293: A Bill for Amendment of the Clean Air Act, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - H. R. 3473: A Bill for the Requirement that the Foreign Claims Settlement Commission Determine the Amount of Claim of Ike Ignac Klein Against the Government of Hungary, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - H. R. 3585: A Bill for Amendment of Title 5 of the Social Security Act, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - H. R. 4007: A Bill for Establishment of a Federal Motor Vehicle Insurance Guaranty Corporation (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - H. R. 4007: A Bill for Establishment of a Federal Motor Vehicle Insurance Guaranty Corporation (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - H. R. 4862: A Bill for Amendment of the Internal Revenue Code of 1954 (Also Contains H. R. 15465), 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - H. R. 4998: A Bill for Establishment of an Emergency Program of Direct Federal Assistance, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - H. R. 4999: A Bill for Establishment of a Commission on Trading Stamp Practices, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - H. R. 5053: A Bill for Amendment of Titles 1, 4, 10, 14, 16, 17, and 19 of the Social Security Act (Also Contains H. R. 16321), 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - H. R. 5054: A Bill for Amendment of the Program of Health Insurance Benefits Under Title 18 of the Social Security Act, 1965; 1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - H. R. 5140: A Bill to Exclude from Income Certain Reimbursed Moving Expenses (Also Contains H. R. 17390), 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - H. R. 5324: A Bill to Provide Time Off Duty for Government Employees to Comply with Religious Obligations (Also Contains H. R. 8919), 1965; 1967 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - H. R. 5714: A Bill for Amendment of Title 28 of the United States Code (Also Contains H. R. 8373), 1965; 1967 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - H. R. 5715: A Bill for Amendment of the Federal Hazardous Substances Labeling Act (Also Contains H. R. 13758), 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - H. R. 5410: A Bill for Authorization of the Issuance of Cost-of-Living Savings Bonds (Also Contains Related Bills), 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - H. R. 6115: A Bill to Provide for the Establishment of a Drug Stamp Program, 1965; 1967 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - H. R. 6116: A Bill for Amendment of the Public Health Service Act (Also Contains H. R. 12816), 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - H. R. 6874: A Bill for the Relief of Giuseppe Caruso, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - H. R. 7069: A Bill for Amendment of the Immigration and Nationality Act, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - H. R. 7070: A Bill for Amendment of the Public Health Services Act (Also Contains H. R. 1027), 1967 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - H. R. 7832: A Bill for Establishment of a Federal Sabbatical Program, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - H. R. 7833: A Bill for Amendment of Section 3 of Title 4 of the United States Code (Also Contains H.R. 14853), 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - H. R. 8141: A Bill to Assist in the Provision of Housing for Elderly Persons (Also Contains Related Bills), 1962-1963; 1967 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - H. R. 8283: A Bill for Amendment of the United States Housing Act of 1937 (Also Contains H. R. 11139), 1964; 1967 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - H. R. 8284: A Bill for Amendment of the United States Housing Act of 1937 (Also Contains H.R. 11142), 1964; 1967 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - H. R. 8285: A Bill for Amendment of the United States Housing Act of 1937 (Also Contains H. R. 7920), 1963; 1967 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - H. R. 8286: A Bill for Amendment of the United States Housing Act of 1937 (Also Contains H. R. 11205), 1964; 1967 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - H. R. 9371: A Bill for Amendment of Title 5 of the United States Code, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - H. R. 9372: A Bill for Amendment of the Internal Revenue Code of 1954 (Also Contains H. R. 17391), 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - H. R. 9422: A Bill for Reclassification of Certain Positions in the Postal Field Service, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - H. R. 9588: A Bill for Amendment of Title 2 of the Social Security Act, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - H. R. 9858: A Bill for Amendment of the Immigration and Nationality Act, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - H. R. 10063: A Bill for Amendment of Title 7 of the Housing Act of 1961, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - H. R. 10064: A Bill for Amendment of the Federal Voting Assistance Act of 1955, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - H. R. 10065: A Bill for Amendment of Title 13 of the United States Code, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - H. R. 10666: A Bill for Amendment of the Older Americans Act of 1965, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - H. R. 10740: A Bill for Making Columbus Day a Legal Holiday (Also Contains Related Bills), 1963-1965; 1967 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - H. R. 10957: A Bill for a Comprehensive Program for the Care and Control of Alcoholism, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - H. R. 10958: A Bill for Full Opportunity and Social Accounting Act, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - H. R. 11180: A Bill for Amendment of the Elementary and Secondary Education Act of 1965, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - H. R. 11215: A Bill for Amendment of Title 28 of the United States Code, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - H. R. 11238: A Bill for Amendment of Immigration and Nationality Act, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - H. R. 11806: A Bill to Safeguard the Consumers During Financial Transactions, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - H. R. 12054: A Bill for Amendment to the Federal Cigarette Labeling and Advertising Act, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - H. R. 12120: A Bill to Provide Federal Assistance to Courts, Correctional Systems, and Community Agencies to Increase Their Capability to Prevent, Treat, and Control Juvenile Delinquency, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - H. R. 12129: A Bill to Provide for Orderly Trade in Textile Articles, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - H. R. 12155: A Bill for Amendment to the Public Works and Economic Development Act of 1965, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - H. R. 12281: A Bill for Productive Employment Opportunities for Those Who are Unemployed or Underemployed, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - H. R. 12401: A Bill for the Housing Act of 1949, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - H. R. 12547: A Bill for Abolishment of the Death Penalty, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - H. R. 12742: A Bill for Incentives for the Creation of Additional Employment Opportunities for Residents of Urban Poverty Areas, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - H. R. 12743: A Bill for Private Enterprises to Provide Adequate Housing in Urban Poverty Areas, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - H. R. 12828: A Bill to Supplement the Purposes of the Public Buildings Act of 1959, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - H. R. 13123: A Bill for Amendment of the Elementary and Secondary Education Act of 1965, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - H. R. 13242: A Bill for Amendment of Title 1 of the National Housing Act (Also Contains H. R. 11137), 1964; 1967 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - H. R. 13243: A Bill for Amendment of Title 1 of the Housing Act of 1949 (Also Contains H. R. 9021), 1965; 1967 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - H. R. 13272: A Bill for Amendment to the International Claims Settlement Act of 1949 (Also Contains H. R. 3474), 1965; 1967 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - H. R. 13278: A Bill for Establishment of a Small Tax Division Within the Tax Court of the United States, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - H. R. 13498: A Bill for Amendment to the Nurse Training Act of 1964, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - H. R. 13991: A Bill for Amendment of the Merchant Marine Act of 1936, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - H. R. 14244: A Bill to Provide to Every American a Full Opportunity to Have Adequate Employment, Housing, and Education Free of any Discrimination (Also Contains H. R. 13358), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - H. R. 14302: A Bill to Facilitate the Transaction of Certain Business Incident to the Representation of a Congressional District in the House of Representatives, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - H. R. 14492: A Bill to Assure Every American a Full Opportunity to Have Adequate Employment, Housing, and Education Free of any Discrimination (Also Contains H. R. 13358), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - H. R. 14493: A Bill to Assure Every American a Full Opportunity to Obtain Adequate Employment and Employment Training, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - H. R. 14494: A Bill to Assure Every American a Minimum Wage of $2 an Hour, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - H. R. 14495: A Bill to Assure Every American the Full Opportunity to Obtain Employment Free from Any Discrimination, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - H. R. 14496: A Bill to Provide Monthly Family Allowances for the Care, Education, and Advancement of All American Children, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - H. R. 14497: A Bill to Assure Every American a Full Opportunity to Obtain Adequate Housing for Himself and His Family, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - H. R. 14498: A Bill to Assure Every American a Full Opportunity to Obtain Housing for Himself and His Family Free from Any Discrimination, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - H. R. 14499: A Bill to Assist Local Educational Agencies to Carry Out Programs for More Effective Schools, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - H. R. 14500: A Bill to Assure a Full Educational Opportunity Beyond High School for All Americans Through Long-Term, Low-Interest Loans, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - H. R. 14779: A Bill for Establishment of the Travel Incentive Act of 1968 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - H. R. 14852: A Bill for Authorization of the Coast Guard to Study Methods of Preventing Casualties Involving Vessels Carrying Certain Contaminants, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - H. R. 14929: A Bill for the Relief of Certain Distressed Aliens (Also Contains H. R. 14806), 1968 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - H. R. 14962: A Bill for Authorization to Reimburse States on the Interstate System, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - H. R. 14971: A Bill for Amendment of the Federal Power Act (Also Contains Related Bills), 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - H. R. 15147: A Bill for Amendment of the Immigration and Nationality Act, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - H. R. 15543: A Bill for Amendment of the National School Lunch Act, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - H. R. 15883: A Bill for Amendment of the Public Assistance Provisions of the Social Security Act, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - H. R. 15891: A Bill for Supplemental Appropriation to Carry Out the Economic Opportunity Act of 1964 (Also Contains H. R. 15388), 1968 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - H. R. 16003: A Bill to Require Federal Agencies to Pay Compensation for Moving Expenses (Also Contains Related Bills), 1968 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - H. R. 16169: A Bill for Creation of an Advisory Council on Guarantees, Warranties, and Servicing, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - H. R. 16290: A Bill to Increase Funds Authorized for Existing Programs to Build Low- and Moderate-Income Housing, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - H. R. 16357: A Bill to Assist Local Educational Agencies to Carry Out Programs, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - H. R. 16460: A Bill for Amendment of the Vocational Education Act of 1963, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - H. R. 16515: A Bill for Amendment of the United States Housing Act of 1937, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - H. R. 16516: A Bill for Amendment of Title 2 of the Social Security Act, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - H. R. 16730: A Bill for Authorization of Sale of Panther Jet Fighters by the United States to Israel, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - H. R. 17097: A Bill for Establishment of a Department of Consumer Affairs, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - H. R. 17145: A Bill for Establishment of a Commission on Hunger, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - H. R. 17339: A Bill for Amendment of Title 2 of the Social Security Act, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - H. R. 17411: A Bill for Protection of the Freedom of Choice of Federal Employees in Employee-Management Relations, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - H. R. 17568: A Bill to Provide for the Disclosure of Certain Information Relating to Certain Public Opinion Polls, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - H. R. 17931: A Bill for Amendment of Title 18 of the United States Code, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - H. R. 17932: A Bill to Disarm Lawless Persons and Assist State and Federal Enforcement Agencies in Preventing and Solving Gun Crimes, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - H. R. 18367: A Bill for Amendment of the Vocational Education Act of 1963, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - H. R. 18451: A Bill for Amendment of the Act of March 3, 1905, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - H. R. 19990: A Bill to Establish a Sonic Boom Damage Fund, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - H. Res. 264: A Resolution for the President to Reduce the Number of Arab Refugees on the Relief Rolls of the United Nations Relief and Works Agency (Also Contains Related Materials), 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - H. Res. 689: A Resolution for Permanent Peace in the Middle East, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - H. Res. 854: A Resolution for the United States Ship Forrestal Tragedy, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - H. Res. 866: A Resolution Concerning Rhodesia, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - H. Res. 999: A Resolution Proposing Cease-Fire in Nigeria, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - H. Res. 1010: A Resolution for Achieving a Stable and Durable Peace in the Middle East (Also Contains S. R. 155), 1967 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - H. Res. 1025: A Resolution for the United States Ratification of the Conventions on Genocide, Abolition of Forced Labor, and Political Rights of Women, and Freedom of Association, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - H. Res. 1078: A Resolution for an Investigation and Study of the Relief of Lieutenant Commander Marcus Arnheiter and Captain Richard G. Alexander, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - H. Res. 1109: A Resolution for the Delay of Restoration of Diplomatic Relations with Egypt, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - H. R. 1135: A Resolution for the United States Enter Into an Agreement with the Government of Israel for the Sale of Military Planes, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - H. Res. 1293: A Resolution for Condemnation of the Invasion of Czechoslovakia, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Housing, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Housing and Urban Development Department (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Housing and Urban Development Department (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - H.U.D.: Seward Park Urban Renewal Project, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - "I" Names, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Immigration, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - "J" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Judiciary Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - "K" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Krebiozen, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - "L" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - "M" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Maritime Administrator, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Merchant Marine Academic Year 1968-1969, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - "N" Last Names, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Narcotics, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - "O" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Committee to Save the Neighborhood Service Centers, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Emergency Loan Conference, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Head Start Transfer, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Izzy Zerling Youth Recreation Center, Inc., 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Lower East Side Neighborhoods Association Proposal for Community Organization and Planning, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Lower East Side Service Center, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Lower East Side Urban League Proposal of Multi-Ethnic Street Work Operation, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Lower West Side Community Center Nutrition Project, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Lower West Side Community Progress Center, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Lower West Side Community Progress Center Proposal for Emergency Family Loan Program, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Mobilization for Youth, Inc. Proposal for a Demonstration Project, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Mobilization for Youth, Inc. Proposal for Federal Juvenile Delinquency Program, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Mobilization for Youth, Inc. Proposal for New Health Occupations Program, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Neighborhood Youth Corps, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Project Elderly Neighbors of Clinton, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Project FIND, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Summer Programs for Lower East Side at Cardinal Spellman Center, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: VISTA, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Women's Talent Corps, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Y.W.C.A. West Side Branch, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - "P" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Parcel Post Bill: H. R. 99, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 23)